<Document>
  [color=#ff0000]HULLROT[/color]

  HULLROT is an 18+ roleplaying game. Some content might be considered explicit to some audiences. If you find certain materials offensive, this may or may not be the place for you.
  It goes without mentioning ERP is strictly forbidden, anyone caught doing this ingame will be removed from the round with a significant time out. This isn't the place for that.

  HULLROT is a roleplaying project and all participants of the game build the environment that creates an interesting and enjoyable story. Members not respecting the setting of the game will not be present again.

  As the name suggests, Taypan - the void where the game takes place is not a kind and forgiving place and we create it together. You will die and separate with your belongings - don't let this get to you and never let down your mask despite the circumstances. Evil exists in this world and is condoned in many cases. For instance, sabotaging the main reactor of the enemy's base to blow it up is smart and effective tactic, punish them for their lack of oversight. Though if this becomes repetitive, the game can quickly get sour and boring for all parties involved and quickly turn into an e-sports event.
  Killing another player is a quick and effective method of resolving a conflict but try your best to keep it interesting. Hostages are often worth a lot more.



  [color=#ff0000]Rules:[/color]

  1. Everyone is here to have fun. Obviously, keep it PG. No slurs, or harassment that extends beyond the usual post-round banter between two sides. Be nice to eachother.
    1a. Obviously no slurs ingame. For clarification, racial remarks, or derogatory wordage.
    1b. This obviously doesn't include any IC terms someone created to refer to another person. Such as; 'Izdom'.

  2. Maintain roleplay naming conventions. People with silly names, or names referencing IRL politicians, etc, WILL be removed.

  3. Play a real person. As fun as it is to be a psychopathic murderer, try to play a person in the setting. While light fragging is alright, repeated reports of people fragging for no reason at all may have you shown the door for low player quality.
  (NOTE: You really have to be doing this beyond the extreme for us to take action.)

  4. Maintain immersion. No fourth wall breaks, or referencing a meme IC, please. Keep to the roleplay!

  5. 'Portstriking', otherwise known as attacking a faction's spawnpoint before the grace period ends is prohibited. Portstriking, even in lesser forms is not allowed.
    This includes; Raiding a faction's armory. Stealing materials from a faction's spawn point. Any hostile action taken on, or just outside of the station.
    5a. Portstriking is only permitted when discussed with an admin, or the current Storyteller of the round, prior to end of grace period.
    5b. Portstrike protection for faction bases is void if;
      - A ship attacks, then flees to their base within five minutes of initial contact.
      - The port takes hostile action against ships within it's vicinity.
      - The Jackal and the Hunters Refuge are not eligible for Portstrike protection.



  [color=#ff0000]QnA[/color]
  [color=#ff0000]Q:[/color] Where can I join the discord?
  [color=#00ff00]A:[/color] https://discord.gg/S5VTFSwPEe (permanent link)

  [color=#ff0000]Q:[/color] Where can I find the lore?
  [color=#00ff00]A:[/color] There is currently no centralized location for the lore. Find out ingame, ask others, or weave your own when the round requires it.

  [color=#ff0000]Q:[/color] When does the server go up?
  [color=#00ff00]A:[/color] The game is tested erratically, and usually on weekends. Not every weekend is a guaranteed testlaunch. Uptimes can be found on the Discord.

  [color=#ff0000]Q:[/color] Where can I find the source? Can I contribute?
  [color=#00ff00]A:[/color] https://github.com/MLGTASTICa/Hullrot. You are encouraged to make pull requests on this github.

</Document>
